We have kept our ID card.  This has to be returned.
Hey mom, you are dubbing it wrong.  This
way, this way.  Let me give you a little idea of
how my journey started.  You marked your attendance last time.
It has already happened.
Sir has come to help me in writing the mail.  Now
Rashi is reading my message.  Ok brother, the
surrender request has been burnt.
I was inside for 20 minutes.  Brother, I did not understand anything.
Now I will take whatever you guys say.
What is this?
Finally brother, I am finally going to give you the laptop.
I'm signing in last time.
Yes, he will say it.
Tell me when will you come back from Hong Kong?  Let's see,
come soon.  Work life gets a bit
messed up.  To tell you the truth, all the children who play become
fat.  I do
n't get time, friend.  There
is one more thing in ICICI Bank.  Sickly you can take unlimited.
Guys, welcome to another video.
It's my 30th and today is my final last day brother.  Yes.
How happy he is.  I don't know anything
brother.  I am happy, I am sad but it is the same mixed
emotions.  Today I will live my last day to the fullest
in my organization ICICI Bank
which has always supported me for the last 2 years and for
which I have done work.  And he has
taught me a lot.  Three-four of my bosses must have
changed like this in two years.
Earlier I was in Gurgaon on MG Road.
Then I, Gopal Das, came to Bara Khambha Road.
Then I am working in Connaught Place.   In the
meantime, I have changed three to four bosses.
No one changes so quickly.  Look, the boss gave me a lot of love.
All the bosses gave me a lot of love.  I
loved you very much.  I saw this
except one or two starters.  No.
Brother, no one made me love you in Gurgaon.
And as soon as I came to Delhi, brother,
I got so much love, Touchwood
Puneesh sir, man, he was very nice.
Right now my boss is Nitesh Sharma.  He was my
colleague.  He is three-four years
older than me.  He is also very supportive.  Before that
Gaurav Sir was super supportive.  So friend, touch wood, I have
met some very nice people.  I got a very good
organization to work with.   To
learn the basics.  And it is one
of the top banks of India and the work culture was
so strong.  We had parties every day.
We used to go to eat and drink.  No matter how much
we told the boss to feed us, he would keep
feeding us.  So friend, touch wood, I
met some very nice people.  And somewhere, if
you do good work, I feel that
you also meet good people.
So let's start the day with this.   Let's take a
quick bath now.  Let's do the puja.
And today is going to be a very
interesting day.  We have kept our ID
card.  This is our
bag to return.  This has to be returned.  F is mine.
But the SIM in it has to be returned.  For now, let's
drink some of this bitter root juice.
Amla, beetroot, bottle gourd water and
we eat our bread.  Ok?  A little
is fine.  I am in a hurry too.  I am also going timely.  I have
mixed emotions but as I
told you I am very excited
for the future and if you guys are new to the channel
then please subscribe, it
motivates me a bit, I get a little push
that I am doing good work and
you guys are connected to me so you guys are
enjoying it, basically I
need some of your support so please subscribe, like,
share,
subscribe all the phones of your houses and support me well,
okay apart from that I am
not taking anything to eat to the office today because there will be a
party in the office, there is going to be a lot of
parties today and I will behave like this today.
Papa is doing puja right now.
So let Papa do the puja.  I am leaving this bag behind today.  I am
taking this one.
Now let's eat it comfortably.
Brother, this is going great.  Paneer Vaneer,
brother, mom is also going down with me.
Then mom will go out for a walk from there.
I take a moment to say goodbye to mother.  Let me take your
blessings for today one last time.
Hey Lucky, it's bad.  Hey,
where are you going?
Where is Maji?  Yes first of all
Maa ji today is my last day, I have no one so please
bless me all the best thank you
and today I am going with my I card and Y card, I have
never worn it till date, I
am wearing this today, you tell me what is going on, okay
come on take care, be happy Maa ji, I am happy
in your rule, enjoy the party, we will
party to the fullest today, yes come on bye, oh
Maa ji you are dubbing it wrong, this side, this
side, oh that side, face this side, hands this side, one,
yes come on come on, ok bye bye bye, I
hope I come soon, okay sir take care,
ok bye Jai Shri Ram, two rickshaw
pullers were fighting, Bhaiya, are you seeing,
sit in mine, come and sit in mine, I said
Bhaiya, why are you fighting, Bhaiya, I will
sit in theirs first, come on, the red one had come first.
Meaning he had also come back.
He hit reverse gear.  Let me
give you a little idea of ​​how my journey started.
May 26 I went to Hyderabad for my ICICI
Bank induction.  These are all vlogs.
You can also go back and look.
After that, from the first or second of June, I started working here as a
deputy manager.  The
one whom DM calls Deputy Manager.
What happened after that, friend, look, I think
I worked in Gurgaon for four months in June, July, August, September,
on MG Road, after that, there was a
lot of problem in travelling, friend.   That
means I used to go from my home to Gurgaon.  It took an hour and a
quarter to an hour and a half.  Then I sent
mails to HR and their
seniors and got my location changed.
So
in October 2023, I came to 12 Khambha Road,
which is called Gopaldas Bhawan.  So
I worked there for I think not five to six
months but more than six months.
In between, I also went to ITO to do some work.
Near ITO, there is our Firozakotla
Cricket Stadium and Arun Jaitley Stadium is
near it.  Ok?  Went there.  After that I
came here to Connaught Place.  Which is my A9
Fells Building A Block.  Connaught Place A
Block.  So this is how the whole journey was like and there
is a lot of pressure in banking.  If you
think that after watching my vlogs, he is having
fun.  It's not like that.  keep working.  There will be
no pressure.  But at times,
when the people above are under pressure,
they put it on you.  Otherwise, friend, keep it chill
and at the end it depends on your boss.
So I told you a little about this journey.
I got placed through MBA
and here if you are from a good college then
you also get the post of Direct Manager which
is M1.  Different banks have
different criteria.  I was a
deputy manager of our bank over here.
After that you become a manager.  If you have a good college
, a private college or even if the
fees of your college are high, then also you get it.
So there are two or three such things.
Now once I take you upstairs, I will
show you my office.  So the office's not place you
no it's Uniqlo on the side.  There's Rare Rabbit
and this is my office.  This is the retail
branch below.  Ok?  Where you guys walk in.
Above this are corporate offices.  So that's where
I sit.  I will go upstairs and
show you.  First of all let me show you my
seat which is my actual seat
where I never sit.  So this
is our operation area.  We entered here and let me show
you once we go inside.   Will
come from inside.  Hi Guys.
So this is our area of ​​operation.  We will enter here.
That is my gate.
This Hanuman ji is here.  This Priyam Preeti, I will
take this home.  This is my client's calendar
he gave me.  Puneet Sir sits there.
So I keep chatting because
Puneet Sir has also left this position.
Now let me show you the actual seat which is
above me.  All the
documents come here.  All the
documents come here.  People verify everything.  We are
waiting for our
documents.  This is our Kundan Bhai.
Very good.  I am a bit busy right now.
Everything happens here.  On top of that we
bring the client's documents.  Or the
client comes here directly and
gives it here.  Then we keep
talking up and down that brother, this is a
rejection.  Their signatures are mismatching, this is this, that is that.
So there are many things.
Here we go to the second floor.  The second
floor is where I
am in transaction banking.  We are sitting here.  Look at this.
Let me show you my seat one by one.
All the cabins are for seniors.  This one
is also a seniors cabin.  I will actually show you.
I definitely sit at the back.
Whenever I get a seat, this is my area
here.  Because here
my entire team sits here.  Otherwise I
will sit downstairs and there will be no network downstairs.
So this also remains.  Lots of things.  Let's
sit here comfortably now.  But this is someone else's
table.  You have an ID card, right?  I am very happy.  I am
very happy today.  And this is my office
bag.  Now there is a lot of work to be done.  The most important thing is to
submit my laptop.
I card has to be submitted.  You have to
submit your bag.  Submit your charger.
I have written my name as Vaam.  Have to
party.  There are a lot of
parties to be held today.  Ok?  So these people are under
pressure.  I am not.  I
marked my attendance 10 times.  This is done
for today.  My attendance.
Hey, incorrect PIN
brother, incorrect PIN is coming friend, so brother,
look, I have opened the app and
marked the attendance, your attendance has been marked for
today, we have to write a message for that to our entire
department, now I am not able to understand what to
write, write a formal message saying bye, the
subject for that, so I understood the
subject, I am writing that from a
banker's journey from a banker to influencer,
but I am not able to understand what to write in it,
so for that I am going down, I
sit with Puneet sir, I ask him,
then tell me whatsapp, today is
our last day and we are vlogging the
journey, that is why
today I have put my I card, these are
our colleagues, they handle retail,
hello, today this is our ICICI Bank entry from there,
how is the retail power going,
we miss you, we will miss you too, there is a lot of pressure, there
is pressure, tell them the reality, friend, there is a lot of
pressure.  Don't believe anywhere.  I am looking for a rich
boy to marry.
So you have a boyfriend.   I will
tell them.  If I am not with him then
I will have to work, so that is fine but
now I am thinking of finding a rich boy.
So that I don't have to do any work to
eat.  Can I put this on the blog?
Yes.  There is no problem, right?  Okay,
friend, for them.  I have also got an ID card for them.
Find a rich boy for her, friend.
All the household work is done.  It is the best.
What what?  I know all the
household work like sweeping, mopping, washing utensils and cooking is also fine
brother I need your help find me a
rich boy who can do all the work,
not all the work that earns money, she will do all the work
madam, okay apart from that friend
we used to come down here basically to
create synergy and what used to happen is that this is the
retail sector, people from here used to
tell us that you meet customers,
introduce us too, they used to tell us that you have
big customers, you introduce us to them, so this is how
our synergy used to be, so
I will miss this also and this is the oldest
branch 7, it was good, it was a fun
experience, I don't know what will happen in future, what will
not happen, but whatever happens will be good
and ma'am's blessings are with us,
look to start some new work one has to take some
risk and we keep thinking that we will do it, if we do it then do it
today itself, we will see, Jai
Shri Ram, say go ahead, sir has come to
help me, tell me what does sir say in writing an email
?  Letter to Success.  Letter to
Success Needs Yes.  A person yes, person
by the way I wrote the email.
Wrote a couple of lines with this.  To succeed needs a person to say
yes.
Push Push
Themselves?  Themselves themselves or
themselves?  Themselves.   I
will tell you.  wait.  Look
how much work there is.  Everyone is helping us.
Posting mail.
Hey friend, let it be done, friend, sir, tell me this is my
user ID and password, sorry brother, look,
I have written this, you guys please read it once, after pausing, I am
sending it now, I will send it,
now Rashi is reading my message, so
you will drink lemonade, make two lemonades
and do not put much masala in one, make
one more paneer sandwich, make one of their bread
pakoras, friend,
brother, get the table cleaned a little,
friend, let's eat snacks, I do
n't eat samosas or anything like that.  Sir said let's go and I will
eat a sandwich.  A sandwich with cheese,
I can eat that.  That is normal.  Yes
brother, please clear this.  Thank you
bread.
Put a good amount of cheese in the base sandwich.
Nice one.  Here comes the lemonade.
Ok.  It's great.  Sir, will you please move
this aside?  Take this and eat.
Jumbo Sandwich.  Who just ate a sandwich today.
Still eating sandwiches today.   Please
surrender the SIM, sir.  Right now I am sitting and
surrendering my SIM.  So I am
submitting his request.  That's what I'm seeing.
Selection of product mobile number
and approval mandatory.   He is the one who is
not letting me select.   I do
n't know, there is some problem.  But right now
I am sitting here and surrendering my SIM
because it is mine.
You get the SIM from the office.  It is also possible that
you may not take the SIM.  You can also use your personal phone.
So all these things happen.  Ok brother, the
surrender request has been burnt.  My
new team is going to lunch right now.  Farewell lunch.   Will
any of you sit in the front?
That's the office.
come on guys.
Sir, can I take your photo?   Should I
not take it?
So I am not going without asking sir.
You and I are going to eat food.
We haven't eaten yet.  You
can eat food for at least an hour.
Going to her bed.  So friend, let's see
where we can go to eat now.  Let's eat and drink something.
And that's it, let's have lunch one last time.
Today is our I Am Zero fight.  So
brother, this is my green apple Mohit.
I am drinking this.  And for me, it's garlic
bread.  These people are eating something of their own.
I am not looking at that side because I
am vegetarian.  So, you are enjoying it, friend.  It's the last
moment.
Cake will also be cut at 5:00 pm.  Brother, these
people have brought me here to buy clothes or a
gift for you.  And you are asking me
what do you want?  You
would like to say something about the fact that you people are asking me to
buy a gift.  take what?  She was speaking.
What were you saying?  Would have taken it.  Should I
not say anything?  No, no, nothing brother.
Let's exit from there, from here.
Brother, I am feeling so awkward.  These
people are saying that we are getting something for you.
Or you tell me what you want?  Or
we will take it ourselves.  Now brother, he has
no dressing sense.
I said, take whatever you want brother.   He is
saying that you again have a problem with your size.  Now
they have brought me here so that you can check the size and try
wearing it.
Where are we going now?  Now we're going to
Uniqlo.  So brother, we have come to Uniqlo.
We saw these two shirts.  Let's see now.
Yes brother,
this one if you want.  You can see.   I don't
want it, right?  Everything
seems the same to me.  Yes, but you want floral, right?
Yes, so he asked, what is your preference
?  I said it is not flower-leafed.  I am going to
Jaipur, I will wear that and go out
because there is a Haldi ceremony there.  You
can see top shoulder t-shirts.  Friend,
I don't like them on me.
Everyone knows which clothes look good on me, which are the ones
my mother brings for me.
They just look good.  So something like that is the
Tiger Plain Shirt.  The trousers below are
loose ones which are in trend these days.
Guys, give me five
minutes, I will tell you what I am buying. Brother, I am
wearing this Charap clothes, I have just tried them, I am
not able to understand anything, they all look the same to me.
I
was inside for 20 minutes brother, I could not understand anything, now I will buy whatever you
guys say, I found out that
this is called Chinese collar, this is like this, here we have
finalized this one, what is this, what is this,
oh
what is it.  Well, I know what's in it.
Sir, should I open it in Vogue right now?  If you permit
Kabir, hold it here.
Sir, you also come.  Son,
people are coming to eat now.  Move away.
How much did you get it for?
Wow brother, show me.  So brother, this is poison.  This
is Ajit.  This is Kabir.  This is me.  Sorry this
is Puni sir.  This is me.  This is me.  Rashi
Akash Sir.  I didn't know how young people looked.
This is Ajit.  Wow friend, thank you so much sir.
Thank you sir for your cooperation.  I mean for
you, in this I will not drink water in the morning when
mom gives me water.  And you will
always be in my heart.  Okay guys,
moving up now.  Now we will cut Sir's cake.
okay brother.  I don't know who is doing 450.  It's
455, sir's
farewell is in 5 minutes.  So let's keep our stuff.
Finally brother, I am finally going to give you the laptop.
Now we will go down to our IT
department and give them the laptop.  The journey
was very tough.  You guys think if there was
no pressure in banking.  There
is a lot of pressure but you should know how to manage the pressure
and keep in mind that all jobs
are difficult.  I repeat everything over and over again.
All jobs are difficult but only those who
learn the work will survive.  If you
think that you know the work without learning it, then it will not happen.  It takes
time initially.
Butt becomes adolescent in learning things.  Brother, I have
given the laptop here.  Brother, I am
signing the last ball.
TM Operative TXP I Bang Delhi
Welcome, I will submit it here again, come on sir, bye, thank you, come on brother,
sister, now let's go to cut the cake,
now it will be the farewell, come on sir, come on, come on,
now it's our farewell, we will enjoy it,
brother
Pradeep brother, give me the spoon,
brother, this is my cake.   You have
come here for a goal.  It's
your time to show up for that goal.  Don't be like
others.  Time will pass.  There are people who are 11 years old too.  There are
people who are 20 years old and there are
people who are 4 years old.  B. The Star.  Not
useless.  Ok?  To have them capability.  Show
case.
Ok?  Let us go.  All the best.  If you have ever
heard it somewhere, then brother, I apologize for that with folded
hands and say goodbye to this amazing building.
By going to this place I would cherish the moments
I spent here.  Thank you so much
and I will remember you all.  But a turn to
Not Coming on the Blogs But May Be My
Pics and Something Will Be There.
Tell me when will you come back from Hong Kong?   Let's see,
come soon.  Okay friend, it
's okay.  It was a wonderful journey with you.  All
the best dear and
let's keep growing.  Let's make game prop
thank you so much sir.  Thank you.  Come on friend, come on
sir.  Ok, see you.  Ok.
Stay connected and I will keep coming home.  Ok.   If you have
any work from my end, please let me know.
100% ok.  Okay, tell me.  You all will
give your numbers.  Yes listen Ajit Bhai whatever it is I have a
very mixed feeling but there is one thing that you have to keep in
mind which is that if you have
taken a decision for some particular thing
then you have to do that thing somehow and if you have
taken a risk then it should be fruitful,
you have taken the decision after thinking carefully so do it now for
whatever reason we have taken the decision, so this is what is
going on in my mind, okay because
look no one leaves even half of a good salary
these days
but okay friend if you want to follow your passion then do that,
finally first of all let's
enjoy for a month, one month means next month what if there is no
job again, no we will do something of our
own now, sir this was given by Puneet sir, I was
getting it, I did not eat it, I don't know, it was a
make puff, sorry sir this was given by my team, they
took me to get it selected, we do
not know your size.  Well, they were saying off white.
This is a Chinese collar.
I found out the first time.  This is a Chinese collar.
Look, this cup was given by Puni Sir.  Well, you have
made it.  Yes, this is our entire team.
I picked this up and brought it.  Ok.  When I got this house, I
brought my card and gave him shoes.  A
group did.  Here it is.  Sir, they took me for this also yesterday.
That you choose.  Good shoes.  So that was it, friend.  It was
not good, man.  I mean it was a
good experience for me for two years and
Hanuman ji also helped me, okay I will
put it on the table, these are from Shimla, so friend I will
say one thing that it was a good experience,
many of you are just getting
placed in ICICI Bank from college, so I will
not be able to tell you everything in this video, but yes
you can put your questions in one place
in the comments and whatever questions you have,
I will try to answer them, but
before that I have already
made videos regarding this bank.  I did
not take the name of the bank of course due to
you know reasons.  But now I have left
so I am telling you.  So
go and have a look and don't ask about salary and all that
because it varies from college to college.
And this is something which is
you know confidential.  So I will not
tell this.  But otherwise, if you want to
ask anything regarding work life balance,
you can just drop a comment.  And work life gets a
little messed up.  To tell you the truth, all the
children who play become
fat.  I don't
get time, friend.  I would just fight and leave.
But yes, it was very difficult for me to
maintain work life balance.
Videos, reels and shots used to come on time
because brother, a lot of hard work had to be done.
Genuinely I am not throwing it away.
But those who are in the banking sector or any
NBFC or those who are currently in FSI,
they know how it is.  So, there are a
lot of problems and stress in every profession.  There
is a lot of tension.  This was our journey, friend.
We have also done packing for this evening.  Mom's bag is
disassembled.  I have to take this small one.
Come, I am not getting my hair cut.  He's trimming his beard a bit.
I shaved my beard.  Look, today she is making it
completely short.  is streaming.   I did it
well and came back.  We have completed the preparations by performing the
puja and now we will have our
dinner.  Dinner is chole.  I have ordered it from outside,
mom.  More homemade pumpkins in the house.
Why does this pumpkin look so dark?  Is it
made in the embroidery?   Have you
put mango in the pumpkin?  Mango means it must be getting sweet.
Yes.  I made it sweet
in pumpkin.  And this white one.  Come on, the white cedar is being cut.   Till then
we will eat this.
Take some onion, cucumber and chutney.   The
pumpkin is growing well.   I am
eating it with chutney.
This is also going well, mango.
I told you this before I even ate the mangoes.   It is
also getting better.
Will eat Safeda.  You guys didn't tell me.
Do tell us in the comment section
which is your favourite mango?  Chaunsa,
Langra, Gulab Jamun, Dasheri, Malta, Safeda,
whatever you like, there are many more.  Tell me one more.
AlphaGo.  Mummy is telling me something.  I just made it
smaller.  Mummy has got her hair cut.   Made them
too small for mom.   Made it
very small.  So why get it cut?  They seemed right.
Hey, we have to get some relief from the
heat but it is very small, so you
told him, no brother, stop, pause, what should I
say, the lock has become
so fat after eating the party,
come, come, you have
finally become free today, you are a free bird,
come, give me the stuff, nothing, no one, give it to me, come,
mother, come, oh friend,
mother has come, yes, I have
eaten too much, I am not able to climb, come,
mother, come, come,
what about you, mother, mother is inside, she is packing the bags for
tomorrow, see,
this has been given by Puneet sir, Puneet sir has given,
our entire group is in it, come, first
come inside, I will switch off the lights,
father is doing puja.   I am a
little late.  Look, he gave me those shoes too.
Who?  Our team.  And I have given you a shirt to
wear.  He took me away.
Took me for shoes.  Liked and took me for the shirt.
Like it.
And I brought this too.  He also brought his cards.
Brought everything.  Come on.  Now you also come.
You are loving these things so much.
You left the job.  Mother, love means
that is mother.  These are memories.
This glass was inside it for memories.  Come over there.  it is
hot.  The AC is on.  Come on.
I turn off the lights.  So mother,
I have
kept the shoes that I am taking here.  Come on.  So our bags are
packed.  Here it is, I will keep this stuff in the morning.  I will
keep the laptop.  So look, mom is
preparing to take my medicine.  So
after you put water in it and take the medicine and drink it, then
after taking a round in it, keep it in this.  Now
put the glass in this, brother, you people might be wondering
what happened, you know that I am
going to Jaipur tomorrow, that is why preparations are going on.
I kept the medicines in this.
All the medicines have been kept in it.  Ok ji thank you.
Mother, I will take all the medicines.  Let me edit everything from A
to Z here.  How did you like
today?  How did you like me, mother?
I know I felt good today.  What did you like
?  I know I was thinking, brother, when will this day
end?  It feels like I have been
released from jail.  It seems as if mother has been released from jail.  Did
not get released from jail.
O friend.
Hey brother, Bhaji Vaji's humor is number one.
Brother, whose grandmother is this?  I got it from them only.
All this humor that I keep saying in between,
no he he hoon.  But mother,
today was the day.  I don't know, I was thinking
since morning that when will this end, when will
I leave the day, when will I go back home.  That's what
I was thinking the whole time but it was good.  It was
fun.  No, it is like a
small child goes to school, yes he
makes excuses like I am having fever today.
I am having stomach ache.   I take
leave.  Correct.  No no, this happens.
This happens not only with children but also with us.
Took sick leave.  Have you ever done this?
But fortunately I have never done this.  I never took
such sick leave.  Well, there is
another thing in ICICI Bank, you can
take unlimited sick leave.  But yes, after some time it happens
that you get a doctor's
certificate, what is it called
?  Medical certificate has to be given.
So I think you can take two leaves consecutively.  If there is a
third leave, you have
to show the medical certificate.  Apart from this, it
also happens that if you
take more than a particular amount of leave
in the whole year, then money is deducted from your bonus.
Someone told me this, I am not very
sure that this does not happen.  I did
not take this risk because I did not want
my bonus to be reduced.  But this can also happen.
So if you are planning to go to ICICI Bank then
make sure that you keep these things in mind
before joining the organization.  Ok
?  So let's conclude the vlog here.
Mother, let's finish the blog then.  Thank
you so much guys for watching the video.  Don't leave
without liking it.  Turn on your post
notifications you will get notified every
single time I post a video and yes we will see
you guys in the next video till then
like and subscribe
this piece